<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.9</title>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 10:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>390</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.9</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 3.9 – Advanced Customization & Enhanced Control! 🎨</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Advanced Dock Customization:</strong> Take control of your dock's appearance with new opacity, blur, and background color options. Create the perfect dock that matches your style and workflow.</li>
            <li><strong>Copy-Paste Dock Settings:</strong> Easily apply the same settings across all your docks with our new copy-paste functionality. No more manually configuring each dock individually!</li>
            <li><strong>Manual Collapsible Direction Control:</strong> We've removed the buggy auto-direction feature and given you full control over how your docks collapse and expand. Set the direction that works best for your setup.</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Full-Screen Behavior:</strong> More consistent and reliable dock behavior when working in full-screen modes across all your applications.</li>
            <li><strong>Fixed App Reordering Bug:</strong> Resolved issues with reordering applications in the dock, ensuring smooth and reliable app management.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 Technical Improvements</h3>
        <p>This update includes numerous under-the-hood enhancements that improve stability, performance, and overall user experience. We've listened to your feedback and made ExtraDock more powerful and customizable than ever.</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're continuing to work on exciting new features and improvements. Your feedback helps us prioritize what to build next, so keep those suggestions coming!</p>

        <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock community. We're committed to making your dock management experience better with every update.</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg"
                length="2836373" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="/2rFYAs72JjF4t4AGTfpOpencvGXMHSqGnq3uO1Mx47LlQkMssmMzxPgsx/5h8w6HMRCqL+VAXgGaoPU3XPuCg==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
