<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.9.3</title>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:54:39 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>393</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.9.3</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 3.9.3 – Smart Widgets Expansion! 📊</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Stripe Widget:</strong> The perfect companion for business owners and entrepreneurs! Add your Stripe restricted API key (safely stored in your macOS Keychain) and monitor your gross and net sales volumes directly from your dock. Choose your preferred time period and watch your business metrics at a glance – all fully configurable from the widget settings!</li>
            <li><strong>IP Address Widget:</strong> Stay connected with your network information! This handy widget displays your public IP address right in your dock. Need to share it? Just click to instantly copy it to your clipboard – it's that simple!</li>
            <li><strong>Universal Widget Customization:</strong> Every widget now comes with powerful customization options! Change colors, adjust fonts, modify sizes, and even configure custom click actions. Make your widgets truly yours and perfectly integrated into your workflow.</li>
            <li><strong>Refined Widget Layout:</strong> We've enhanced the overall UI and performance of the app, making widget layouts more consistent and ensuring they fit beautifully in your dock alongside your other items.</li>
            <li><strong>Performance Boost:</strong> Experience smoother interactions and faster responsiveness across all widgets and app features.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 Technical Improvements</h3>
        <p>Behind the scenes, we've optimized the widget rendering system and improved the overall architecture for better performance and stability. The Stripe integration uses industry-standard security practices, with all API keys stored securely in your system Keychain.</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>The widget revolution continues! With Clock, Spacer, Stripe, and IP Address widgets now available, you have incredible power to customize your dock experience. We're already exploring new widget ideas based on your feedback – the possibilities keep growing!</p>

        <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock community. Whether you're tracking your business metrics or just keeping an eye on your IP address, we're thrilled to see how you use these new widgets in your daily workflow!</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg"
                length="4132355" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="qEKJoj85sUZwsT8pi+bM+MLyJ3bS8RX34qzHpKUhY7nLIJwRW5U9PLBrTVHaewY/mFmJ8LQnC7KBUb6wcx3dAg==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
