<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.9.1</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:42:20 +0300</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>391</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.9.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
             <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 3.9.1 – Major Refactor & Enhanced Features! 🚀</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Complete Code Refactor:</strong> Fully refactored codebase enables faster development and eliminates inconsistent app behavior for a more reliable experience.</li>
            <li><strong>Optimized Resource Usage:</strong> Breaking down large components into smaller, lightweight ones dramatically improves app performance and responsiveness.</li>
            <li><strong>Enhanced Full-Screen Recognition:</strong> "Hide on Fullscreen" now works better with improved full-screen detection across all applications.</li>
            <li><strong>Full macOS Tahoe Support:</strong> Complete compatibility with macOS Tahoe, including all ExtraDock functions and features.</li>
            <li><strong>Fixed Light Mode UI:</strong> Resolved invisible button issues in Light Mode for better accessibility and user experience.</li>
            <li><strong>Global Settings Hub:</strong> New centralized settings panel for global preferences, license management, and launch options.</li>
            <li><strong>Dock Renaming:</strong> Added option to rename "Dock" to "User Interface" to match your preferred terminology.</li>
            <li><strong>Dock Border Customization:</strong> New border customization options to personalize your dock's appearance even further.</li>
            <li><strong>Copy/Paste Settings:</strong> Easily transfer settings from one ExtraDock to another with our enhanced copy/paste functionality.</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Versioning:</strong> Moved to better versioning format (v1.38 → v3.9.1) for clearer tracking of major and minor releases.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 Technical Improvements</h3>
        <p>This major update represents our most comprehensive refactor yet, focusing on performance, stability, and future-proofing ExtraDock. The enhanced architecture delivers faster responses and more consistent behavior across all features.</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>With our new foundation in place, we're accelerating development on exciting new features. Your feedback continues to shape our roadmap!</p>

        <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock community. This release sets the stage for even bigger improvements ahead.</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg" length="3082151" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="xsZZqSabCN4pAXbHY+2+cM5mcScip/B7i02f1vBrJjENWxDycrzeE2GeyZ8Oy+SFDMf6bbDxYbMU8YJCdpWFCw=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
