<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>4.1.6</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 22:01:05 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>416</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>4.1.6</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 4.1.6 – Total Dock Control! 🎛️🚀</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Dock Space Reservation:</strong> Your fixed docks now reserve their screen space! When you maximize or zoom a window, it stops at the dock edge instead of hiding behind it. Works automatically with expand-style resizes, with an optional "Active on Drag" mode for manual window moves too.</li>
            <li><strong>Native macOS Trash Integration:</strong> The Trash widget now offers a Native Trash mode that connects to your real macOS Trash. See a live item count from your actual Trash folder and drag files to trash using Finder — no more virtual-only trash. Switch between native and virtual mode anytime!</li>
            <li><strong>Hotkey Auto-Hide Timer:</strong> Show your dock with a hotkey and it auto-hides after a set delay (3–60 seconds). Moving your mouse over the dock pauses the timer, so it stays visible while you're using it. Perfect for quick-glance workflows!</li>
            <li><strong>Left Click Behavior Options:</strong> Customize what happens when you click a dock icon — Normal for standard app activation, or Toggle Minimize to click-minimize and click-restore. Your dock, your rules!</li>
            <li><strong>Hide File Extensions:</strong> Non-app items like documents, scripts, and files can now hide their file extension for a cleaner dock appearance. Configure per-item through the new item settings window.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔔 Smarter Notification Badges</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Full Count Display:</strong> Badges now display the full notification count instead of capping at 99+.</li>
            <li><strong>Dynamic Badge Sizing:</strong> Badge size automatically adapts to the number of digits for a polished look.</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Reliability:</strong> Thread-safe polling and crash-safe preference saving keep your badges rock-solid.</li>
            <li><strong>Better macOS Tahoe Support:</strong> Deeper accessibility traversal and fallback mode for more reliable badge detection on macOS Tahoe.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🛡️ Safety & Reliability</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Drag Removal Confirmation:</strong> Accidentally dragging items off the dock is now protected — a confirmation dialog asks before removing an item.</li>
            <li><strong>Automatic Folder Repair:</strong> Folders that were incorrectly detected as apps are now automatically repaired on load, with a manual "Repair Folders" button available in dock management.</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Trash Widget Config:</strong> The Trash widget settings panel has been redesigned with clear toggle switches and a collapsible permissions section — no more dense text walls.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🐛 Bug Fixes</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Fixed Vertical Dock Shifting:</strong> No more unexpected shifting when badge counts update on macOS Tahoe.</li>
            <li><strong>Hardened Persistence:</strong> Improved stability during drag reorder and system sleep.</li>
            <li><strong>Fixed Multi-Add Rollback:</strong> Resolved issues with multi-add rollback in dock management.</li>
            <li><strong>Smoother Hotkey Timer:</strong> Improved hotkey auto-hide timer pause on mouse interaction.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're continuing to push the boundaries of dock customization! More features, more widgets, and more ways to supercharge your workflow are on the way. Keep sharing your feedback and ideas — you're shaping the future of ExtraDock!</p>

        <p>Thank you to the amazing ExtraDock community for your continued support. Together, we're building the ultimate dock customization experience!</p>

        <p><em>Want even more control over your workspace? Check out <a href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/">DockFlow</a> to manage dock presets and create the perfect setup for every task!</em></p>
        <p><em>And <a href="https://extrabar.app/">ExtraBar</a> to create the ultimate menu bar that fits your workflow!</em></p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/v4.1.6/extraDock.dmg" length="7749360" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="VZ3N6PSeS6gDL2+JtwuQ9mLTVLWS6RSQfA/Glao8hsyy6MJtsVFNQL+iMBQWPUfRNc1vtQmybcJL7JjaNvjiBA=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
