<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>4.1.2</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:33:29 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>412</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>4.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 4.1.2 – Multi-Monitor Perfection! 🖥️</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Rock-Solid Multi-Monitor Support:</strong> We've completely refactored dock position handling to ensure your docks stay exactly where you placed them! No more unexpected shifts across displays when reopening the app.</li>
            <li><strong>Smarter Screen Recognition:</strong> New screen resolution strategy with improved fallback mechanisms ensures reliable dock positioning even when monitor configurations change.</li>
            <li><strong>Post-Launch Position Validation:</strong> New DockPositionValidationService validates and corrects dock positions after app launch, ensuring accurate restoration based on your preferences.</li>
            <li><strong>Seamless Dock Appearance:</strong> Docks now wait until position validation completes before appearing, eliminating visual jumps during app launch.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🎬 Fullscreen App Compatibility</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Fixed Screen Switching Issue:</strong> Interacting with the dock while using fullscreen apps no longer causes unexpected space or screen switches. Your current workspace stays intact!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 Auto-Hide Enhancements</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Edge-Sensitive Reveal:</strong> Auto-hidden docks now respond when your mouse approaches screen edges, making the feature more intuitive for docks fixed to left or right positions.</li>
            <li><strong>Smoother Animations:</strong> Configurable show/hide animation durations provide smoother transitions when the dock appears and disappears.</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Mouse Tracking:</strong> Added a backup polling mechanism that ensures consistent mouse tracking behavior even when the dock is hidden.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🎯 Widget Improvements</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Live Configuration Updates:</strong> Widget settings now apply immediately without requiring multiple selections or re-opening the configuration panel.</li>
            <li><strong>Better LiveDock Widget Sizing:</strong> The LiveDock widget now automatically recalculates dock size when visible items change, with proper positioning adjustments.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 General Improvements</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Enhanced Collapse/Expand Settings:</strong> Improved settings experience for a better user experience.</li>
            <li><strong>Better State Persistence:</strong> Improved dock state persistence and restoration logic for more reliable behavior.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're continuing to enhance the ExtraDock experience based on your feedback. More features, more polish, and more ways to customize your workspace are on the way. Keep sharing your ideas – you're shaping the future of ExtraDock!</p>

        <p>Thank you to the amazing ExtraDock community for your continued support. Together, we're building the ultimate dock customization experience!</p>

        <p><em>Want even more control over your workspace? Check out <a href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/">DockFlow</a> to manage dock presets and create the perfect setup for every task!</em></p>
            ]]></description>
                <enclosure url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/v4.1.2/extraDock.dmg" length="7414884" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="OW28LLBGPq/S7MZNzFN0kPnTOpKJm78WfbihHxornIPiE0BlUUt4NniwUwID6/UYZjum9eNJzKm7Pcv9u/7IBg=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
