<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>extraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.6</title>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:38:07 +0300</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>360</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.6</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
             <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <h2>Welcome to ExtraDock 1.36 – A New Chapter Begins!</h2>
                <p>We’re excited to announce ExtraDock 1.36, our first major release since joining the AppIt Studio family! This update marks the beginning of a new era for ExtraDock, as we set out to elevate your experience and take the app to the next level.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Enhanced Performance:</strong> We’ve optimized the core of ExtraDock for smoother, faster, and more reliable performance.</li>
                    <li><strong>All-New Management Screen:</strong> Easily access a redesigned management interface from the menu bar, making it simpler than ever to customize your dock properties.</li>
                    <li><strong>Drag Indicator:</strong> A new visual indicator makes dragging items on your dock intuitive and effortless.</li>
                    <li><strong>Improved Drag & Drop:</strong> Enjoy a more responsive and fluid dragging experience throughout the app.</li>
                    <li><strong>Smarter Dock Name Positioning:</strong> Dock names are now displayed more clearly and consistently.</li>
                    <li><strong>Better Collapsible Dock Experience:</strong> Collapsing and expanding your dock is now smoother and more visually appealing.</li>
                    <li><strong>And Much More:</strong> We’ve made numerous under-the-hood improvements and bug fixes to ensure ExtraDock is the best it’s ever been.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock community. We’re just getting started—stay tuned for even more exciting updates!</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg" length="2619533" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="7p2tow+WHs8SH9Mq0NuArFhMIruf7a02O9h22ad44fqX3v2IER176IgT2MbaAM35orPRQXADPjqzwbpM90ygAQ=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
