<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>4.0.8</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:34:48 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>408</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>4.0.8</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 4.0.8 – Tahoe Polished & Rock Solid! 🏔️</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Enhanced macOS Tahoe Support:</strong> We've continued refining ExtraDock for macOS Tahoe! More compatibility improvements ensure everything works seamlessly on Apple's latest and greatest.</li>
            <li><strong>Redesigned Dock Settings Panel:</strong> The settings panel for your docks has been improved for a cleaner, more intuitive experience. Customize your docks with ease!</li>
            <li><strong>Smarter Screen Recognition:</strong> ExtraDock now recognizes your screens more reliably, ensuring your docks always appear exactly where they should – especially great for multi-monitor setups!</li>
            <li><strong>More Stable Hide/Show Behavior:</strong> We've enhanced the dock visibility system for smoother, more consistent show and hide functionality. Your docks now respond more reliably to your commands!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🐛 Bug Fixes</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Item Relocation Fix:</strong> Fixed an issue where items moved from their original source location weren't being found properly. ExtraDock now smartly relocates these items, keeping your dock organized even when files move around!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🎯 Built from Your Feedback</h3>
        <p>These improvements came directly from your reports and suggestions! Your feedback helps us squash bugs and polish the experience. Thank you for helping us make ExtraDock better every day!</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're always working on new features and improvements based on your feedback. Keep sharing your ideas – you're shaping the future of ExtraDock!</p>

        <p>Thank you to the amazing ExtraDock community for your continued support. Together, we're making the ultimate dock customization experience!</p>

        <p><em>Want even more control over your workspace? Check out <a href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/">DockFlow</a> to manage dock presets and create the perfect setup for every task!</em></p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg"
                length="6891407" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="ZCAxI7zZmjH648kXnjTtoxp5UeXKsyZvD5tGfm1g9PFnB/0SunS9VzSFmvVzO+BGCQHKZum+wFTcFWhbBaF9Ag==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
