<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.8</title>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:09:27 +0300</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>380</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.8</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 3.8 – Redesigned UI and Enhanced Features! 🎉</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Complete UI Redesign:</strong> Experience ExtraDock like never before with our fresh, modern interface that's both beautiful and functional.</li>
            <li><strong>Redesigned Menu Bar Items:</strong> Clean, intuitive menu bar interactions that make accessing ExtraDock features effortless.</li>
            <li><strong>Cleaner Dock Experience:</strong> We've removed dock names from the display to create a minimalist, distraction-free workspace that fits seamlessly on any Mac.</li>
            <li><strong>Rock-Solid Stability:</strong> Extensive bug fixes and performance improvements ensure ExtraDock runs smoother and more reliably than ever.</li>
            <li><strong>Under-the-Hood Magic:</strong> Significant technical improvements that enhance speed, responsiveness, and overall app performance.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>💭 We Value Your Feedback</h3>
        <p><em>Missing the dock names feature?</em> We'd love to hear from you! If you found dock names helpful and would like us to bring them back as an option, please reach out. Your feedback directly influences our development roadmap.</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're already hard at work on the next version, which will bring even more powerful dock controls and customization options. Stay tuned for more exciting updates coming your way!</p>

        <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock journey. This is just the beginning of what we have planned for you.</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg"
                length="2743422" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="siL4j2R82rThZfrajxlIvZ9CunspNH0P/5pPks/TWK73DZBVkP4R03jhYBkfvdgJx7IylggQnzbqt9kpSHcgBQ==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
