<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>3.9.2</title>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 19:23:38 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>392</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>3.9.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 3.9.2 – Widgets Revolution! 🎨</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Widgets Support:</strong> Introducing a revolutionary new widget system that transforms how you customize your docks! This game-changing feature opens up endless possibilities for personalization.</li>
            <li><strong>Clock Widget:</strong> The latest addition to our widget collection! A fully customizable clock that supports themes, sizes, timezone settings, and much more. This powerful widget showcases just how far we can take this feature – it's the perfect example of what's possible with ExtraDock's widget system.</li>
            <li><strong>Spacer Widget:</strong> Add custom spacing between dock items to create the perfect layout that matches your workflow and aesthetic preferences.</li>
            <li><strong>Enhanced Visual Customization:</strong> Take your dock aesthetics to the next level with powerful new options for borders, backgrounds, opacity, and blur effects – make your docks truly unique and beautiful.</li>
            <li><strong>macOS-Style Edge Spacing:</strong> New option to add default spacing from the edges of the screen, giving your docks that authentic macOS look and feel.</li>
            <li><strong>Design Refinements:</strong> Multiple design fixes and improvements throughout the app for a more polished, professional experience.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🔧 Technical Improvements</h3>
        <p>The new widget architecture is built for extensibility and performance, ensuring smooth operation while leaving room for exciting future enhancements. Every widget integrates seamlessly with ExtraDock's existing features.</p>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>The widget system is just the beginning! With the Clock widget now available, you can see firsthand how powerful and versatile our widget system can be. We're already working on bringing you even more exciting widgets in the near future – the possibilities are endless!</p>

        <p>Thank you for being part of the ExtraDock community. We can't wait to see how you use widgets to create your perfect dock setup!</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/prod/extraDock.dmg"
                length="3609806" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="uWR+XvBEna85AWZzWxuB7ZxPQSpoSBHMUnw8X0JTY6atADsX/7gMMuVzJxxtW75sFUnbWOdU5tzp+Hf+vy6wCw==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
