<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>4.1.5</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:04:50 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>415</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>4.1.5</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 4.1.5 – Space Awareness Has Arrived! 🚀🪐</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Space Awareness Widget:</strong> Brand new widget! Space Awareness shows you which apps have windows open in your current macOS Space, giving you instant context about what's active on each desktop. Stay on top of your workflow without ever losing track!</li>
            <li><strong>Minimized App Retention:</strong> Minimized apps stay visible in the Space Awareness widget so you don't lose track of them when switching focus. No more hunting for hidden windows!</li>
            <li><strong>Per-Screen Scoping:</strong> Space Awareness items are scoped to each dock's screen, so multi-monitor setups show the right apps on the right display. Your workflow stays perfectly organized across all your screens!</li>
            <li><strong>Automatic Cleanup on Space Switch:</strong> Retained apps are automatically cleared when you switch Spaces, keeping the widget fresh and relevant at all times.</li>
            <li><strong>Configurable Left-Click Action:</strong> Choose what happens when you click a Space Awareness item – activate the app, show a menu, and more. It's your widget, your rules!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🐛 Bug Fixes & Improvements</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Fixed Space Jumps from Dock Animations:</strong> Dock frame resize animations no longer cause unexpected Space switches. Your workspace stays exactly where it should!</li>
            <li><strong>Improved Dock Item Classification:</strong> Better detection of package documents when dragging items into the dock, resulting in more accurate item type assignment and icons.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're continuing to expand the widget ecosystem and push the boundaries of what your dock can do! More features, more customization, and more ways to supercharge your workflow are on the way. Keep sharing your feedback and ideas – you're shaping the future of ExtraDock!</p>

        <p>Thank you to the amazing ExtraDock community for your continued support. Together, we're building the ultimate dock customization experience!</p>

        <p><em>Want even more control over your workspace? Check out <a href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/">DockFlow</a> to manage dock presets and create the perfect setup for every task!</em></p>
        <p><em>And <a href="https://extrabar.app/">ExtraBar</a> to create the ultimate menu bar that fits your workflow!</em></p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/v4.1.5/extraDock.dmg" length="7538978" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="D9OTd9GKcsB1zkNSG8KoHv9LvFibFIEgbn8sJS0CpngxMyOTJtOSog87LWzNLDtwDRBUlipZzb0hv7pJAF9kAQ=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
