<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ExtraDock</title>
        <item>
            <title>4.1.3</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:07:11 +0200</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>413</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>4.1.3</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/extra-dock-updates/release-notes.html
            </sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[

        <h2>ExtraDock 4.1.3 – Desktop Widget Mode & Dock Freedom! 🖥️</h2>
        <h3>✨ What's New & Improved</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Desktop Widget Mode:</strong> Turn any dock into a desktop widget! Enable the new "Act as Desktop Widget" toggle in dock properties and your dock will sit beautifully behind app windows like embedded desktop content. Click or drag to interact – the dock smartly elevates to the front, then gracefully settles back after you're done. It's like having a dock and a widget in one!</li>
            <li><strong>Hide Native macOS Dock:</strong> Go all-in on ExtraDock! New global setting lets you hide Apple's native Dock completely. Your original Dock preferences are safely saved and restored when you toggle it back on. ExtraDock remembers your choice across launches – set it once and forget it!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🐛 Bug Fixes</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Safari Web Apps & Aliases Fixed:</strong> Adding Safari web apps, aliases, and symlink items to your docks now works flawlessly! Both drag-and-drop and the Add Item dialog properly resolve all URL types, with smart fallback search across your Applications folders.</li>
            <li><strong>Smoother Upgrades:</strong> Improved data compatibility ensures a seamless upgrade experience – no crashes when updating from older versions!</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>🚀 What's Next?</h3>
        <p>We're continuing to push the boundaries of what your dock can do! More customization, more ways to integrate your dock into your workflow, and more features shaped by your feedback. Keep sharing your ideas – you're shaping the future of ExtraDock!</p>

        <p>Thank you to the amazing ExtraDock community for your continued support. Together, we're building the ultimate dock customization experience!</p>

        <p><em>Want even more control over your workspace? Check out <a href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/">DockFlow</a> to manage dock presets and create the perfect setup for every task!</em></p>
        <p><em>And <a href="https://extrabar.app/">ExtraBar</a> to create the ultimate menu bar that fits your workflow!</em></p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/extra-dock-updates/releases/download/v4.1.3/extraDock.dmg"
                length="7399927" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="UuoQvM2JaFGP4K0OFl2MS05x8jpY+1jvyM+xGxh+M/+z8SyvcJBjCdmd7p8wzDeusLTiietvlW7xDQL8BwBTCQ==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
